sovereignman.co 2017-01-28

# Privacy Policy – Sovereign Man

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter( _Notes from the Field_ ).

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.

We use Google Analytics to analyze our visitor traffic in order to improve our products and services, and as part of that your IP address and time of visit is recorded. You may, however, visit our site anonymously through a VPN, or by disabling javascript in your browser or using a plugin that blocks trackers.

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Sovereign Man website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving our free e-letter _Notes from the Field_ , etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

We use third party services for analytical purposes, and in some cases those services use cookies, and in our secure members area you can choose to allow cookies to enable you to stay logged in.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel at https://sovereign.customerhub.net/ and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms of Use

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.sovereignman.com/terms-of-use/>

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on May 28, 2013

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

admin(Replace this parenthesis with the @ sign)sovereignman.com
